Guide to the Paul Kwilecki photographs and papers, circa 1910-2008, bulk 1960-2008 RL.00790
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Paul Kwilecki photographs and papers
circa 1910-2008
1960-2008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Kwilecki, Paul, 1928-2009
Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University)
Vestal, David
RL.00790
42 Linear Feet 54 boxes; 1 oversize folder; 2 oversize boxes
Collection comprises over 500 black-and-white photographic prints, along with negatives, contact sheets, photographer's notes, journals, writings, speeches, correspondence related to photography, and printed material, totaling over 9000 items. Kwilecki's photographic work documents rural and small-town life in and around Bainbridge, Decatur County, Georgia, an undertaking he began as a self-taught photographer in 1960 and continued until his death in 2009. Subjects include local landscapes, tobacco workers, county fairs, hog slaughtering, cemeteries, churches, courthouses, recreation on the Flint River, local industry, shoppers, downtowns, and house porches and interiors. The themes of race relations and religious life predominate. Many of Kwilecki's subjects come from the African American community in Decatur County. Significant correspondents in the manuscripts series include photographers Alex Harris and David Vestal; the collection includes a small set of Vestal photographs. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Approximately 9480 Items
Biographical Note
Missing Title
1928 Feb. 24 Paul Kwilecki born in Bainbridge, Georgia
1948-1949 (?) Photographs published in Life magazine
1949 B.A. in English, Emory University, Atlanta, Georgia
1960 Began making a photographic record of Decatur County, Georgia
1975 Sold his hardware business in order to devote all his time to photography
1979 Awarded a National Endowment for the Arts Fellowship
1981 Awarded a Guggenheim Fellowship Publication of his first book, Understandings
1992 Publication of Lowly Wise: Scenes of Religion In and Around Decatur County
1994 Nov. 4-Dec. 21 Exhibit: Paul Kwilecki: Decatur County, Georgia, Lehigh University
1997 Oct.-2000 Oct. Traveling exhibit: Homage: Photographs of Decatur County, Georgia, offered by the South Carolina State Museum
2001 Exhibit: Decatur County, Georgia, at Duke University's David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
2009 December 9 Died in Bainbridge, Georgia, age 81
Kwilecki's photography is also housed as part of permanent collections at the Museum of Modern Art, New York, the High Museum of Art, Atlanta, Georgia, the Columbus Museum, Columbus, Georgia, the Lyndhurst Foundation, Chattanooga, Tennessee, and the Albany Museum of Art, Albany, Georgia.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research; however, negatives are closed to use. Digital and print copies available.
Please contact the Rubenstein Library before coming to use this collection.
Provenance
The Paul Kwilecki photographs and papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase and gift from 1991-2010, 2017.
Collection Overview
The Paul Kwilecki Photographs and Papers span the whole of his career and include over 500 black-and-white photographic prints, negatives (chiefly safety but also some nitrate and glass plate), contact sheets, photographer's notes, journals, writings, speeches, correspondence related to photography, and other printed material, totaling over approximately 9000 items.
The bulk of the collection consists of Paul Kwilecki's prints and other photographic material documenting rural and small-town life in and around Bainbridge, Decatur County, Georgia, an undertaking he began as a self-taught photographer in 1960 and continued until his death in 2009. Although Kwilecki developed an interest in photography in the 1940s, only a very small portion of the images in the collection pre-date 1970.
The collection is organized into two major series: Photographic Materials, containing prints, contact sheets, and negatives, and a Manuscripts Series housing many files of correspondence, writings, and other personal papers.
While initially interested in photographing tobacco workers, Kwilecki turned his focus to other subjects, including county fairs, hog slaughtering times, cemeteries, churches, courtrooms, recreation on the Flint River, local industry, bus stations, shoppers, downtowns, house porches and interiors, and landscapes. Many of Kwilecki's subjects come from the African American community in Decatur County. Throughout the collection, the themes of race relations and religious life tend to predominate.
The Manuscripts Series (1967-2008) also provides an interpretation of life in Decatur County but also documents Kwilecki's photographic philosophy and practices. The correspondence and the journals, related to Kwilecki's work and career as a photographer, comprise the largest groupings. The series also contains Kwilecki's personal journals, dating from 1967-1969; Kwilecki's printing notes; news clippings; exhibition brochures; and a brief internet biography of Kwilecki. Many of Kwilecki's writings attempt to express in words the same topics he tried to illuminate through photography.
Additional manuscripts (14 boxes) and photographic materials were received in 2010 following Kwilecki's passing away. They include many folders of correspondence dating from 1971-2008, arranged in original order either chronologically or alphabetically by folder title. Significant correspondents include photographers Alex Harris and David Vestal; the collection also includes a small set of Vestal's photographic prints. Other files contain writings, clippings, and other items. The writings include journals from the 1970s; typed excerpts from early 20th century Georgia newspapers, some on racial incidents; drafts of Kwilecki's talks; and notes for the Decatur County photography publication (one folder). A few publications round out the last box in the collection.
The negatives are closed to use; contact sheets and prints offer alternate access to Kwilecki's images. Eleven nitrate large-format sheet negatives, dating from approximately the 1940s-1960s, are slated for digitization. Also included in the collection are several glass plate negatives by an unknown photographer dating perhaps from the 1910s.
Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Separated Material
Paul Kwilecki's personal library of dozens of books on photography and other publications was cataloged separately for Duke University's David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, with a few titles also going to the Perkins Library general collections. For assistance on locating these titles, please contact Research Services in the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library.
African Americans -- Georgia -- Decatur County; Cemeteries -- Georgia -- Pictorial works; Church buildings -- Georgia -- Pictorial works; Courthouses -- Georgia -- Pictorial works; Documentary Photography -- Southern States; Photographers -- Correspondence; Photographers -- Georgia; Photographers -- Southern States; Religious life -- Georgia; Rural African Americans -- Georgia; Tobacco -- Cultivation -- 20th century; Bainbridge (Ga.) -- Pictorial works; Decatur County (Ga.) -- Pictorial works; Georgia -- Pictorial works; Georgia -- History -- 20th century; Georgia -- Race relations -- History -- 20th century; Georgia -- Social conditions -- 20th century; Georgia -- Social life and customs; Black-and-white photographs; Contact prints; Cellulose nitrate film; Contact sheets; Diaries; Gelatin silver prints; Glass plate negatives; Negatives (photographs); Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University); Harris, Alex, 1949-; Kwilecki, Paul, 1928-2009; Vestal, David
- Decatur County Court House, 1966-1998; 3 folders 83 prints
  Scope and Contents
  Kwilecki assigned a unique number to each print, indicating the roll number, month and year, and frame number. However, quite a few have no print numbers. When titles or dates are not present, they have been supplied in brackets by the processing archivist.
  Prints in this series are arranged in rough chronological order (though never consistently so), and there are several subgroupings.
  Descriptive captions are supplied by Kwilecki. The title Understandings has been added to the descriptions for prints which appear in that 1981 photobook published by Kwilecki.
  - Mother and son waiting outside court room, 1981 Jan. (Understandings) (Box PHO 1, Print 12-181-3)
  - Outside court room. Second floor, 1987 Sept. (Box PHO 1, Print 10-987-13)
    Scope and Contents note
    With its white walls to diffuse incoming light and overhead flourescents, the light is unbelievably soft, as I've tried to indicate.
  - Three judges, 1979 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 154-1179-7a)
    On the wall a picture of Judge Crow (deceased). Standing, Judge Robert Culpeper. Seated, Judge Wallace Cato.
  - Three men talking in front of court house, 1970 (Understandings) (Box PHO 1, Print unnumbered)
    A typical scene outside court house.
  - A typical scene outside main entrance when court was in session, 1977 Aug. (Box PHO 1, Print 89-877-24a)
  - Prisoner cleaning court room, 1979 Sept. (Box PHO 1, Print 118-979-22)
    The tattoo had beads sewn beneath the skin and was in colors.
  - Family sitting on floor at bottom of steps, 1975 (Understandings) (Box PHO 1, Print unnumbered)
    Waiting in vestibule.
  - View from grand jury room looking toward Willis Park, 1979 July ( Understandings) (Box PHO 1, Print 97-779-13)
  - Prisoner with a bush hook cleaning Darsay family cemetery in the southern part of the county, 1983 June (Box PHO 1, Print 33-683-5)
    It is the oldest cemetery in Decatur County. Joel Darcy was one of the original settlers here in 1823.
  - Prisoner cleaning up Oak City Cemetery, 1986 Aug. (Box PHO 1, Print 16-886-36a)
    Prisoners who have committed non-violent crimes are used to clean up cemeteries, repair roads, cut grass along highways, etc.
  - Spectators, 1981 Jan. (Understandings) (Box PHO 1, Print 15-181-7)
    This was a session of 'State Court,' not Superior Court. Judge Robert Galpin is on the bench.
  - Corner of court room, 1981 Jan. (Understandings) (Box PHO 1, Print 8-181-8)
    Looking from court room into jury room. Witness stand is at left.
  - Temporary court room, 1998 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 55-1198-14a)
  - Jury room before remodeling, 1977 July (Understandings) (Box PHO 1, Print 62-777)
  - Main entrance, 5:00 a.m., 1996 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 27-496-12)
  - Main entrance, West Street, 1996 Oct. (Box PHO 1, Print 31-1096-5)
  - Marriage in the ordinary's office, 1981 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 1: 51-481-9)
  - Marriage in the ordinary's office, 1981 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 2: 51-481-10)
    Couple getting married by the Ordinary (judge of the Probate Court). The witnesses in the background are her mother and father and this couple's child.
  - Marriage in the ordinary's office, 1981 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 3: 51-481-11)
  - Outside grand jury room, 1980 Apr. (Understandings) (Box PHO 1, Print 42-480-11a)
  - Outside court room. Solitude, 1979 Nov. (Understandings) (Box PHO 1, Print 157-1179-14a)
  - Court house seen from North Broad Street, 1986 Jan. (Box PHO 1, Print 4-186-5)
  - One end of the jury room, showing rest room facilities, 1975 Mar. 17 (Box PHO 1, Print unnumbered)
    The black and white of the toilets have nothing to do with segregation. This was the only restroom in the jury room and was used by men and women, white and black alike. The court house has been remodeled and the jury room no longer looks like this.
  - Woman and child waiting anxiously outside court room, 1982 May (Box PHO 1, Print 46-582-29a)
    The pictures behind them are former judges, sheriffs, ordinaries, etc.
  - J.R. Deese, Ordinary, in his office, 1973 (Box PHO 1, Print unnumbered)
    The scales shown on his desk are not those of justice but the original assayer's scales given to the county in 1823 when it was established, against which all other scales were set and maintained.
  - Exterior of the West Street façade and power pole with wires and transformers, 1985 Sept. (Box PHO 1, Print 35-985-3)
    Aside from the visual interest of the pole and its accouterments it will be a reminder of the clutter of our views long after wires have been put under ground.
  - Woman and child walking by main entrance, 1987 Aug. (Box PHO 1, Print 8-887-22)
    Exterior showing the West Street entrance, originally the main entrance. The institutional façade towers over the young mother and her child, suggesting the power of government.
  - People in court room during a session of superior court, 1981 Feb. (Box PHO 1, Print 27-281-12)
    The segregation, which is obvious, was entirely voluntary. The balcony, originally for 'colored' people, had long since vanished.
  - Sherriff Shorty (E.W.) Phillips in front of one of the women's cells, circa 1972 (Box PHO 1, Print unnumbered)
    In the county jail adjacent to the court house.
  - County farm display, 1982 Mar. (Box PHO 1, Print 21-382-6)
    This is a prison wagon used from about 1912-1926. Prisoners working in distant parts of the county slept in this wagon. Imagine eighteen men, exhausted and sweaty, trying to sleep in a low-lying swamp infested with mosquitoes.
  - Prisoner at the County Farm, making cane syrup, 1966 (Box PHO 1, Print unnumbered)
    Behind him, inside the shed, cane juice is being boiled to make syrup. Inmates at the farm grow all the food and livestock that is consumed.
  - Judge Robert Culpepper of the Superior Court holding the docket, about to walk into the court room, 1975 Mar. 4 (Box PHO 1, Print unnumbered)
  - Jury pool, rear of courtroom, 1997 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 40-1197-7a)
  - Spectators, rear of courtroom, 1997 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 42-1197-13)
  - Jury pool, courtroom, 1997 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 40-1197-39a)
  - State court, courtroom, 1997 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 38-1197-14a)
  - Staircase, 1997 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 37-1197-25)
  - Night view, exterior of courthouse, 1996 Aug. (Box PHO 1, Print 22-896-16)
  - Judge A. Wallace Cato on the bench, 1996 Sept. (Box PHO 1, Print 26-996-23)
  - Graffiti on holding cell door, 1996 Aug. (Box PHO 1, Print 23-896-31)
  - View of scaffolding on Court House tower, 1998 Mar. (Box PHO 1, Print 16-398-24a)
    Part of a series Kwilecki shot of prisoners restoring the courthouse.
  - Prisoners, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 20-498-31)
  - Workers, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 26-498-29a)
  - Prisoner, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 22-498-21)
  - Prisoners, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 23-498-11)
  - Prisoners, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 22-498-31)
  - Prisoners, 1998 Mar. (Box PHO 1, Print 15-398-35)
  - Vault lintel in the ordinary's office, 1998 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 54-1198-4a)
  - View of stairway, 1998 May (Box PHO 1, Print 34-598-16)
  - Stairway, 1998 May (Box PHO 1, Print 34-598-20)
  - Northeast corner of courtroom, 1998 Sept. (Box PHO 1, Print 47-998-13)
  - Fireplace in courtroom, 1998 May (Box PHO 1, Print 33-598-20)
  - Prisoner, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 18-498-6)
  - Prisoners, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 17-498-8)
  - Prisoners, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 28-498-5)
  - Prisoners, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 23-498-20)
  - Prisoners, 1999 Jan. (Box PHO 1, Print 3-199-30)
  - Guards, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 18-498-19)
  - Thanksgiving dinner on courthouse grounds, 1998 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 54-1198-27a)
  - Thanksgiving dinner on courthouse grounds, 1998 Dec. (Box PHO 1, Print 57-1298-10a)
  - Prisoner, 1998 July (Box PHO 1, Print 43-798-22)
  - Prisoner, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 23-498-15)
  - Prisoner, 1998 July (Box PHO 1, Print 43-798-17)
  - Prisoner, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 21-498-30)
  - Two prisoners, 1998 Nov. (Box PHO 1, Print 54-1198-13a)
  - Clock tower, 1998 Apr. (Box PHO 1, Print 20-498-21)
  - Decatur County Courthouse (Understandings), 1981 January (Box PHO 28, Print 6-181-29)
  - No known title, 1979 June (Box PHO 28, Print 89-679)
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - No known title, 1977 September (Box PHO 28, Print 95-977)
  - Lobby, second floor, Decatur County Courthouse (Understandings), 1975 (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - No known title, 1978 November (Box PHO 28, Print 104-1178-9)
  - Prisoners and guard working on dam, 1979 (Oversize-box 1, Print unnumbered)
    Chain gang guard watches prisoners building dam to keep water from overflowing highway. Typical swamp.
  - 1983 March (Oversize-box 1, Print 13-383-28)
    This carcass has just been pulled out of the vat of hot water. The convicts have scraped the hide bare. Next step is to quarter.
  - Hog killing at the County Farm, 1983 Mar. (Oversize-box 1, Print 14-383-20a)
    These men are rotating a hog carcass in hot water, preparatory to scraping the hair off the hide.
  - 1981 Dec. (Oversize-box 1, Print 142-1281-8)
    This prisoner from the County Farm restored and refinished this light fixture which originally hung in the court room. Initially it was a gas fixture, later converted to electricity. The brass had been painted over several times and the whole thing was about to be thrown out.
  - A family anxiously waits outside court room, 1980 Apr. (Understandings) (Oversize-box 1, Print 42-480-5)
  - Prisoners over steaming vat, 1983 Mar. (Oversize-box 1, Print 12-383-14)
  - Hog killing at the County Farm, 1983 Mar. (Oversize-box 1, Print 14-383-13)
    Early morning and very cold.
  - 1983 Mar. (Oversize-box 1, Print 13-383-11)
    These hogs are about to be dipped in the vat of hot water.
  - Butchering hogs at the county farm, 1983 Mar. (Oversize-box 1, Print 12-383-9)
    This ritual goes on throughout the county at this time of year.
  - Prisoners at the county farm killing hogs, 1983 Mar. (Oversize-box 1, Print 13-383-34)
    It was a bitterly cold, windy day. This man is removing the brain and tongue from the head of the hog.
  - Butchering hogs, County Farm (prison), 1983 Mar. (Oversize-box 1, Print 13-383-4)
- Cemeteries, 1965-1999; 4 folders 67 prints
  - Statue of Mrs. Cloud, 1978 Nov. (Understandings) (Box PHO 2, Print 110-1178-27a)
    This statue on the grave of a Mrs. Cloud was carved from a photo of her standing in the receiving line of her 25th anniversary party.
  - Cows grazing, lambs watching near cemetery, 1978 Jan. (Understandings) (Box PHO 2, Print 9-1-78-6a)
  - Madonna presiding over collapsed grave, 1978 Feb. (Box PHO 2, Print 23-278)
  - Family cemetery deep in the woods near Climax, Ga., 1979 Feb. (Box PHO 2, Print 24-279)
  - Ornate gate, Oak City Cemetery, 1985 May (Box PHO 2, Print 18-585-8)
    Family plot in Oak City Cemetery. Ornate gate, ancient spreading oak in background.
  - Shedding camelia bush, 1974 (1974 frontispiece for Understandings) (Box PHO 2, Print unnumbered)
  - Wooden grave marker with old glass pitcher in abandoned cemetery, 1983 Dec. (Box PHO 2, Print 75-1283)
  - Union Springs Primitive Baptist Church cemetery in Miller County, Miss. Spooner's grave, 1982 May (Box PHO 2, Print 44-582-7)
  - Bench on Haddon-Belcher lot, Oak City Cemetery, 1986 Jan. (Box PHO 2, Print 1-186-6)
  - Amelia. Photograph on a grave stone, 1983 Oct. (Box PHO 2, Print 57-1083-7)
  - Photo on grave stone, 1980 Nov. (Understandings) (Box PHO 2, Print 108-1180-9)
    Typical country church and cemetery.
  - Child's grave, Oak City Cemetery, 1981 June (Box PHO 2, Print 86-681-8)
  - Grave of two children, Flea Town Cemetery, 1979 Feb. (Box PHO 2, Print 22-279)
    What are the fruit jars for? Flowers? If so, why some lids?
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, Oak City Cemetery, 1965 (Box PHO 2, Print unnumbered)
    Another in the series I made of this statue. From a 5x7 negative contact printed.
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, Oak City Cemetery, [ circa 1966] (Box PHO 2, Print unnumbered)
    From 8x10 negative (lost); only extant print.
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, Oak City Cemetery (wide angle), 1968 (Box PHO 2, Print unnumbered)
    Statue in late afternoon.
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, Oak City Cemetery (dark bkgd, heavily stained, favorite), 1968 (Box PHO 2, Print unnumbered)
    One of many photos I’ve made of this same statue through the years. See my notes for fuller explanation.
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, Oak City Cemetery (with snow), 1972 (Box PHO 2, Print unnumbered)
    Another in the pictures of this figure, this one with snow on it!
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, stained, Oak City Cemetery, 1974 (Box PHO 2, Print 14-179)
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, cleaned, Oak City Cemetery, 1986 Jan. (Box PHO 2, Print 3-186)
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, vandalized, Oak City Cemetery, 1990 June (Box PHO 2, Print 12-690-12)
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, head in flower pot, Oak City Cemetery, 1999 Dec. (Box PHO 2, Print 16-1299-10)
  - Sarah Will Harris statue, restored, Oak City Cemetery, 1991 Jan. (Box PHO 2, Print 1-191-8)
  - No known title (Box PHO 28, Print unnumbered)
  - Oak City Cemetery, main gate, 5:00 a.m., 1996 Oct. (Box PHO 2, Print 31-1096-20)
  - Kneeling figure, cemetery beside highway, Brinson, Ga., 1978 Oct. ( Understandings) (Box PHO 2, Print 85-1078)
  - A corner in Oak City Cemetery, 1975 Nov. (Understandings) (Box PHO 2, Print 7-11-75)
  - Grave of the Countess of Pau and the Duchess de Navarre, Oak City Cemetery, 1987 Nov. (Box PHO 2, Print 22-1187-9)
  - Temple Beth-El Cemetery on a foggy morning, Oak City Cemetery, 1990 Jan. (Box PHO 2, Print 1-190-3)
    View towards the Jewish part of the cemetery.
  - Statues on the graves of Judge Bower's wives, 1968 (Box PHO 2, Print unnumbered)
    These are memorials to two of Judge Bower's three wives. They command the highest ground in the cemetery.
  - All that remains of the fence and entrance to Providence Cemetery in Grady County, 1984 Dec. (Box PHO 2, Print 66-1284-1)
  - Statue on grave obscured by overgrown azaleas, 1982 Mar. (Box PHO 2, Print 3-182)
  - The First Christian Church in Decatur County, 1984 Jan. (Box PHO 2, Print 4-184-29)
    Now abandoned, the church is used to store hay.
  - The Most Wonderful Mother Ever to Live, Greenwood Baptist Church Cemetery, Mitchell Co., 1983 Nov. (Box PHO 2, Print 67-1183-34a)
  - Old Main Gate in fog, Oak City Cemetery, 1976 Jan. (Box PHO 2, Print 5-176)
  - Collapsed grave, 1990 Feb. (Box PHO 2, Print 3-290-1)
    In many cemeteries vault lids are used as gravestones. This one has fallen in.
  - Spooner statues in Union Springs Primitive Baptist Church cemetery, Miller Co., 1980 Nov. (Box PHO 2, Print 113-1180-1)
  - Gone Home, 1982 Dec. (Box PHO 2, Print 122-1282-21a)
    Grave in Negro Cemetery, Bainbridge.
  - Mt. Nebo Cemetery, 1989 Dec. (Box PHO 2, Print 61-1289-3)
  - Griffin cemetery in Grady County, 1984 Dec. (Box PHO 2, Print 65-1284)
    Dr. J. H. Griffin who built this cemetery was from Bainbridge.
  - Entrance to Oak City Cemetery, 1984 Dec. (Box PHO 2, Print 67-1284)
  - Grave of Wanlisa Spear, 1991 June (Box PHO 2, Print 21-691)
    Wanlisa Spear is the girl being baptized on page 113 of Understandings. She had become a drug addict and was raped and murdered on a dark street near her home. Rev. Mitchell performed her funeral as well as her baptism.
  - Wooden grave marker in abandoned cemetery, 1989 Nov. (Box PHO 2, Print 58-1189-6)
  - Family cemetery deep in woods, 1979 Feb. (Understandings) (Box PHO 2, Print 22-279)
  - Grave, Oak City Cemetery, 1997 Aug. (Box PHO 2, Print 22-897-16a)
  - Griffin family cemetery, Attapulgus, Ga., 1994 June (Box PHO 2, Print 16-694)
  - Cemetery, 1994 June (Box PHO 2, Print 16-694)
  - Water tower seen through cemetery gate, 1982 Nov. (Box PHO 2, Print 112-1182-9)
  - Greenshade Cemetery cleaning, 1977 Apr. (Box PHO 2, Print 23-477-17)
  - Greenshade Cemetery cleaning, 1977 Apr. (Box PHO 2, Print 21-477-26a)